[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chinese zodiac is not limited to just defining what animal you are. It also tells you this.", "correct_answer": "Your element", "incorrect_answers": ["Your emotional factor", "Your spiritual age", "Your physical coefficient"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the smallest wombat species on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Southern Hairy-nosed Wombat", "incorrect_answers": ["Northern Hairy-nosed Wombat", "Common Wombat", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of alcoholic beverage is the popular South African drink Umqombothi?", "correct_answer": "Beer", "incorrect_answers": ["Brandy", "Wine", "Rum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Dog Day Afternoon, Sonny asked to see his wife and his wife came. Was her name Leon?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What speed must the time machine in Back to the Future achieve in order to travel through time?", "correct_answer": "88mph", "incorrect_answers": ["80mph", "100mph", "108mph"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The planet Jupiter orbits the Sun at an average distance of how many kilometers?", "correct_answer": "778,000,000", "incorrect_answers": ["77,800,000", "778,000", "7,780,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of car did Benjamin receive for his 21st birthday in the movie The Graduate?", "correct_answer": "Alfa Romeo", "incorrect_answers": ["Ferrari", "Porsche", "BMW"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Czech Republic, Luxembourg and the UK were among the countries with most obese people in the beginning of the new century.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Indian Ocean Earthquake of 2004 did not spark a tsunami.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1979 movie Breaking Away, listed as the 8th best sports movie in history by the American Film Institute in 2008, focuses on this sport.", "correct_answer": "Bicycling", "incorrect_answers": ["Tennis", "Baseball", "Rugby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the movie Dirty Dancing first released?", "correct_answer": "1987", "incorrect_answers": ["1981", "1989", "1985"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what time does Big Ben, in London, have both clock hands together?", "correct_answer": "Never", "incorrect_answers": ["At 12 noon and 12 midnight", "Only at midnight", "Only at noon"]}]